gadget-asia.com 2012-11-11

# Privacy - Gadget Asia

© 2003-2007 Gadget Asia All rights reserved

When shopping at www.gadget-asia.com, safe transactions and the protection of your privacy are our number-one priorities. To help our customers understand our commitment to security and privacy, we've outlined our policy in detail.

**Secure Shopping**  
Gadget Asia believes in providing a safe and secure shopping experience for all of our customers. We provide stringent and effective security measures on our website. We guarantee that every transaction you make at www.gadget-asia.com will be 100% safe. The www.gadget-asia.com site was developed to support secure online purchasing through secure socket layer (SSL) technology. All information that you provide during the shopping process is encrypted for your protection. Furthermore, information provided to us as a result on your online purchase is completely confidential and will not be disclosed or sold to any other party.

**Account Protection**  
If you choose to open an Gadget Asia account with us, your password will be your personal, secret entry code to www.gadget-asia.com. The passwords are encrypted on the database, and therefore cannot be read by anyone who accesses this data. Your password is needed to access any account areas and you can change your password as many times as you like.

**Collection and Use of Information**  
When you place an order, we require you to provide us with personal contact and billing information, including your address. Gadget Asia uses this information to give you a customized experience and to process the orders that you place with us. When you place an order, your account information is saved. Our database stores your personal contact and delivery information, and automatically transfers it to the order form each time you place an order so that you do not have to re-enter this information. When you visit www.gadget-asia.com, we collect some basic non-identifying information. This specifically includes information regarding your operating system, browser software, and IP (Internet Protocol) address. This information is collected in order to provide you a satisfactory service. We may use the information to detect problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

**No Third-Party Use of Your Information**  
Gadget Asia does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to third parties.

**Links to Other Web Sites**  
www.gadget-asia.com contains links to other Web sites. Gadget Asia is not responsible for the privacy practices and content of these third-party Web sites. We urge you to follow safe Internet practices: Do not supply personal information to these Web sites unless you have verified their security and privacy policies.

**Opt Out/Modify**  
Gadget Asia gives you several options for altering or removing your information from the database at anytime.

**Your** **Consent**  
By shopping at our Web site or opening a www.gadget-asia.com account, you consent to the use of your personal information by Gadget Asia in the manner specified in the privacy policy. We, however, have the option to change, modify, or add to the terms and conditions of the privacy policy at anytime. These changes will be posted on the site, to give you notice. Any customer who does not agree to the altered privacy policy has the option to opt-out.
